Just like your god. I want
to drive past. To get
up close but I think. Alice and
the and
I and I. Read about it and
the
authentic and
the I'm.
The AS.
The you.
The the all.
The on.
The side I.
The the.
The the I'm
the. The
.
Why one by one
the song I
was one the
Iraq
the and I changed my
why
why why why why why why why
why why
why why.
Why why
during the
Leura
during
my career. Was.
I that really right now while the mud was
sanitary and all and I never mind I got.
Why.
I'm not sure you're right
about at what. We refer to
a riddle and something wrong on the track
and they want to get around this like no
one controlling not
encourage en route I'm on.
The the little girl I landed
on that the women are
alive. Our getting to keep trying to.
Poison the
poor
the
way.
The unarmed the in
the
Sudan nightmare
why when
the same. Thing all
right. I'll get out of.
Here because now we better get
you back down. What about
the other girl. I don't remember.
During. My
chest.
Why
her. Voice
which.
Is why there were I think by half and I
might go. There and although I know I will
now I'm living the morning now.
That are well Mary oh my God
I'm not going to that hurt we weren't
out of line. That the doctor. It's
not quite the attitude we're going to do
to work I'm not put in about I'm going to
maybe only want more than that course it
doesn't pay much but well at least it's
stuck are you driving my
Bentley the see you both know.
I'm not good I've got mean I'm going to
guys they do marry it takes more than
intellect to be
a musician with your
soul and good or OK good
luck marrying now by Nancy and the next
time you're in thank you but I'm never
coming back.
I don't know about the girls or How To me
they were for years and they she was the
only want to bring girls to survive
an accident that she'd feel
a little something like homeless or
you never know what she thinks you
know it kept pretty much to ourselves and
maybe in her place I do the same thing
just pick up lines again. She so
quiet right see who's you like
my I guess that's what it takes to survive
I still say she's behaving going.
Well this is gonna but I will it'll
go around alone whether you know.
My goodness the
snow globe
my hand my
the
the one
where.
The
Iran
the
eyeball
I.S.I.
The
Iran
the
I.S.I.
Has. The
Iran the
poor
the
the.
The
thank
the
.
The
rock.
Quem vai the the.
VOICE. Murmur
the the.
Whoa whoa whoa whoa.
All right here's.
My help in the lead up I.
Have anything else but it. Could you tell
me what that the the back of your mouth
by the knife all I mean you know
back out that it used to be
a pretty rig late in the old days
and the leg went down and it made
a dent all out of work and they put those
buildings up there made some sort of
a carnival after
a while. That years ago though
it stands out there now I. Ave
app and you have a running How could you
network oh here that is right over here
a little later.
Bank after I left and I rented it yet.
By. When I I'm in the inland
and then we're going to
remember when our I only got
you with the land now how.
Is room. For. You can go
watch. That one. Right things
right you know the one come to
my arm. I want their lives back but now
the young can need them when I want them.
Right goodnight and I'm. I thank.
You why. Why why
why why.
You're.
And this is mishandling this hour
I did. You know I think I made
a thank you I'm wrapping Nicole I swear
we heard about you oh by the way you have
like I had a good. Day We hope you're
going to like it here and we're not
a lot of trips in this area of course but
we haven't won back congregation. We met
him for the reception
they want to be. And I
don't suppose it's an absolute this is
a I don't know what some of the ladies were.
They say I'm not trying to be another
. Course we'll let it go
at that for the time being
but my dear you cannot live in
isolation from the human race to the
minute that night I want you to.
Why why why
why why why why why
when the war with.
More or.
Less than or when
or
why the
Orlando
when the. Man
why. I.
Pour why why. Why
point when you're my
why war
why.
Practical. You needn't break
in here I've got to make
a call out at the lake would
you like come along for
a run. Right but
look at it if you like I work with you
a lot. More
or.
Less that used to be quite right
it's been too good to go
a long run now when you take me good news
no it isn't safe out there any more or
that why they put up this barrier We've
got anything to step around with. What
attraction could there be when you
think I'm not I really and I don't.
Mind that nothing more than
a girl. With you talk
Merican. Like the limit when
the guy aiming for
a minister to break the law wouldn't.
Maybe I can come back the product.
Galley I am now.
When I when.
I read I'm going to need a good.
I want to read about what
a lie. I mean by one guy
with an accent I knew was.
That when. I went back I was.
Getting better. By. Then what I
got that crowd and then it made me
a bad apple I'm glad. I'm the bad one
they didn't end it you know why I
want to make the prior bad not bad.
Thank you. Thank you
Brad. Thank.
The you.
Are doing. Yeah yeah what.
I'm going to nominate the
right that made me do it they
either I want to I'm going to run.
The thank.
Cutting because my manhunt I get
I know I am. Pumped up and they
where are we I could go but we've been
able to know what I've been to new that I
realized. Very quickly but I got in
or met or anything after I had the
I'm not you. Might recognize.
A guy that. I'm going
to arrange my room. For
him on. Her and.
Cannot.
Thank you for. The you.
I am the man thank. YOU
THANK.
YOU
THANK
. YOU THANK YOU.
We have made. My. Doctor
I want. To commend all.
Oh you must mean Until then
you had the rumor the whole
I don't I mean the other one. You know.
Me and you Aneta Linda and I have three
a girl or is it out because you want him
to go there you're going to get in.
The back. Again and I'm
going to hide the board.
Then you know how the Street
works in Miami. I don't.
Now look up that way I have that in there
even though they are there big enough
though that you did high demand even could.
You get that and not let your imagination
run away when I knew the name.
And no but I. Did that when the.
Going to come. If you weigh.
You see.
You've
you've
.
Power.
Out good money I'm your
mama Yeah. I can I have.
But I got
a day off right I make it my will yeah baby
i know i get it. I get ready come over
here I. Got my idea of
hell and to the cause.
I gave her all I'm glad about the
nominees are and I thought well.
I'm glad I didn't and do not know what I
can buy I don't know all of the big worry
the older guy worked no way out
that the. Money the I. But I
got
a couple shots up the last much longer you
have no bank it now the recommended bank
like Original get on with
that what you do I mean
a hey come by the play the organ
in church church. Hey I don't mind
about that I just didn't know you're a
church woman to me attempted to make
a big. Who has a funny way to look at.
People seem shocked because I took
a job in
a church and like I regarded simply the
term I mean there's no organ in that they
didn't. Think like that
to give you nightmares
saying that. Now that we might.
Think feeling that. I can have
a last night myself running. To the night
in the dark you then rather.
Then I think back in place
in bed that no more night oh.
Make the mortgage and. I had to get to be
a church organ I thought
that in college I got
a college. Football but
they want to me to take
a lot of class and think you know who they
are that way I'm just not the next guy
and I didn't think they were teaching in
school you know and the thing I am most
was principal product. You know you know
like the principal product to Brazil.
Coffee being this Neko I feel like that.
I was good I couldn't care less how you
and I care about girls in the article
I. Would have done that with
a graduated. But the man can
you think to come. Come
I would be an alcoholic I just
like to start the day off in
a good mood so you might be led by
a new. Kind of guy employers
want you know the happy worker.
That make your one happy. Morning I get
that right. And they need me in the
lead don't know J.
. Bob I hope I have all
the blame for the law
and thank you Bob We can crank I back
a little but. Some of the
term killer died when I
had laid. In and took
up the wrong impression
I'm
a guy that can do that and I think
I have. I get that either. I
can imagine it but I. Wouldn't you
know I had the baby shopping.
That they had
a nice back we might think the
guy but the other was there and
I'm I'm sure it isn't
that I think it makes
a second Trek but I like that we have the
neck read out of Iran that you write
about here that
I I am
.
You've. Heard.
That the.
The the.
Wrong.
Why.
What is it that. I didn't mean any
harm I just got to get it right
now. What was that my hand. And
I said I was the one out there
I had me do you know why but
I look like you had
a fight if there were you won't solve
anything but control yourself I'm Dr sent
my office is right across
the street. You got
a shot you would like my
assistant public not to offer
a bank could I come again I'll certainly
I'll take over my office with the the
tubes All right.
I'm back with anyone it was
a. Fight and I. Know
I had no play. No part
of the law or me and
then you saw this. Man.
Excuse my back but I want to get some of
that written down I'm not talking for an
hour Anything else anything
you haven't told me. That's
the whole story empowering me that now
that he's doing this that's simple but was
it what do you mean you could hardly been
in the park the seven zero one of us men
would have seen him and that night
in the hallway you said yourself
a man and he came up
a minute later and she didn't see in the
jeep are you driving at in less than
a week since you were in the car the crashed
into the river how you got out of that
no one seems to know that that
experience must have been
a serious emotional shock I think I imagine
got out of it don't you think I mean
then I didn't say that I don't mean
that I'm a competent or anything I'm
a realist I'm not get into imagining
any hogwash all of us imagine things
I've never heard two men talking behind
your back and imagine they were talking
about you that you never imagined you saw
someone you knew and walked up to them
and they were fixed range or I can see
what that has to do with the point is that
our imaginations quite six honest they often
misinterpret what we see and hear you
agree. We're in fact going to
happen in ordinary times go
a step further look we're
going to happen in
a high fever or following us there is
emotional shock. About that I could have
imagined all of this this man this
thing resembling And when you've got
a known and acquaintance or your
father know your wife's been here
a back row now I have no
desire to one never know
right and I say. I think so and
I have no desire within the
company about that have you always
felt this way. I don't know
don't you want to join in the things that
other people do share the experiences of
other people I don't think they were being
that close. Do you know that crap that
I'm trying to reach out for their got the
thing do you feel guilty wanting them. I
don't I'm bad I'm not
a psychiatrist and perhaps I'm being clumsy
and all that but I am suggesting that
perhaps this again represent the guilt
feeling I have that they can all they can
frankly I don't know I know what
my magination are trying to take
are going to put it out there
a song will pass and I want to I thought
about that would you meaning that or
probably end up at the light somehow you
associate it with all that don't you go
out. But and then go back to
I could go on I don't buy
a hasty if it is are my mouth and I
could get it back to or maybe but
at least someone to be with you now I can
I get the No I'm not pregnant to go where
we're primed to go out there
more. Apt to I can go all out.
What
your war one
war
no.
Use.
For war.
Or are.
They act. I don't want to get turned
down again I was thinking that you know.
I found out about you know the way anyway
I had to pack up the test that was good.
About it I got that over
the blade that. I now I
then. Say Yeah do you mind if I had you
what I wanted and then I never saw you
break and then you have paid and then.
This is the old. One right the
call the friendly this morning
I mean the company. May give me
company tonight that and what we
call. The.
City in
a thread I'm going with that the I
have the game I may. Or may. Be
in charge and. Or are.
Or
we've all the
you're.
With.
The Dow hit with.
Our.
Poll. The
our
world. Our.
Poor poor poor.
Or are the
war during.
Our war.
Thank.
YOU THANK. All pain Starkweather
But are you playing
a master of you know research and
real people know what I want.
And I feel sorry for you and your lack
of how this art of the music up the
charts the things have meaning and
significance to us I assume bait it to you
but without this awareness. I'm
afraid you cannot be our organ
incontinence I must ask you to resign.
Me I'm abandoning you nor should you turn
your back on the church there is help
here and I just like that
when I say I've been waiting
a long time for you Mike I'm just over
there I don't just the right place to go.
The same.
Time I don't drink either not really not
really I was as if you don't drink really
ask me that. Out maybe I
not only bring reality I
really director.
If you like the music I like you
don't like it you don't like to.
Drink don't like the man I'll hold you
close to that I didn't say that you have
said anything all evening I don't
play that song again you like
it so much.
A Johnny was
a dom. But you know I'm on I've been holdin
out on me that's not the kind of pick
you usually drag around you could look at
your job see that you're glad you want to
back. Lay off. Of that man
listen I'll help you put it over I don't
want you to think I'm the No. Good
luck. When you know I'm.
A. College. Boy about this girl if you
want me. I want to be
a maid. Said I'm good I
don't like that you know.
That you were. In the scene to join
my company that's not you. I may
be yapping. I'm not and
if you don't I will.
Get my head join
a party trying to. Pay
good money for that stuff any
boy. I am I know you. Know
I don't give you what you stand
a class. That's not me just told me by.
Now with everything I say in the OK
your mouth. Mike I want to be with.
Just with anybody with. The you're.
Feeling all out. Of me
want to be all and I'll be
the No come on. I'm not being
with you really I do. I don't
want to be long tonight.
I want to be near you.
I mean. Yes.
I. Want to you only get out
of. You know my role only
a couple of. Is likely to
get very far from the I've.
Got.
The Enough of it. The bad
I want to get another
one.
At any time I want to
go in there like I was.
And I think you know I
have to be alone and I.
Recommit on that will be a. Good one be
a long time to lead. The
kind. Yeah ask me yet.
Like the little one.
And.
I'm the Rabbi thank you.
And let's Matthew what's
going on around you
I. Was silent you know. BAD BAD me
the I'm getting the do it
now they say that's just
why they get me out
homeworld Balrog the the.
Crash crash crash while I read
noir in the Kremlin
bed I will read
World War
world yet you.
When you can that were not very
much I'm afraid I'm sure glad
you have happened there or I'm gonna
come right back right after I think
I came on purpose I don't think your
boss there ever since she left my office
yesterday What's she been
up to. The devil never was
I heard her going on around that room
all night never heard such goings
on and she wouldn't let me in
her room this morning she's
a strange one. She absolutely refuses my
help I can't say that I blame or there's
something about her that completely baffles
me I urged her to call on me she feels
she needs help and I hope she will. I
can't let us die in their power I want to
worry about she's determined to leave the
city and she wants to get away as soon as
possible I hope she does. I hope she
can.
Keep.
The Yeah. The girl at.
The creek I know you're with the
rat when you go out Rat Pack.
I was.
Pregnant
I was awful I
bought
a wild goose or whatever the
aisle rolled the window
the girl
rag
. And Rabbi grabbed
a new paragraph Guernica. All
wrapped
up the rat. In the car while
jabber but did I get out of
bed the if. It's the.
Why the
I.M.F.
The board I I I I
why
I am
I
my
what my and I remember my
my name
.
The
oral point for.
poor
fellow
the
on.
The or or.
The the. End of the neck.
The the.
The you want to get the. Get away from.
Whole.
The
the.
they took it.
The
Rat had.
The power.
When you're the need drop
the
.
The you.
Are. Reading
R R R R R R R
We're going to work with didn't work
for an immigrant
worker we're not going to go.
Looking for and trying to prevent
me from it didn't work in
the Get me back. I had the
arc I had to work the day
mark. And I wish
my luck. If your god were pressed to come
back I. Try to keep. The to
work in the can work
I. Work
. God I
did
a new thing you do you
good eh ringing
ignore what.
The
Iwo.
Jima the fifth floor
all the all
the
all
crew.
The thank.
The
power. Grid
the poor.
Rural. Group.
All.
Brand
.
My.
Birthday I I called.
You.
My.
Rather ride nightmare
rather
read or write.
You. You.
Our.
Our. Crowd.
Are our.
Nice
AI
Mer. Which.
Caused our weather. Man
up what then Canadian up.
And then mapping.
The.
Why.
Why why.
Why why why. Why.
Do I have.